(Instrumental)
Crashing, hit a wall Right
now I need a miracle Hurry
up now, I need a miracle
Stranded, reaching out I
call your name but you're
not around I say your name
but you're not around I
need you, I need you, I
need you right now Yeah, I
need you right now So
don't let me, don't let
me, don't let me down I
think I'm losing my mind
now It's in my head,
darling I hope That you'll
be here, when I need you
the most So don't let me,
don't let me, don't let me
down D-Don't let me down
Don't let me down Don't
let me down, down, down
Don't let me down, don't
R-r-running out of time I
really thought you were on
my side But now there's
nobody by my side I need
you, I need you, I need
you right now Yeah, I need
you right now So don't let
me, don't let me, don't
let me down I think I'm
losing my mind now It's in
my head, darling I hope
That you'll be here, when
I need you the most So
don't let me, don't let
me, don't let me down
D-Don't let me down Don't
let me down Don't let me
down, down, down Don't let
me down, down, down Don't
let me down, down, down
Don't let me down, don't
Oh, I think I'm losing my
mind now, yeah, yeah, yeah
mind now, yeah, yeah I
need you, I need you, I
need you right now Yeah, I
need you right now So
don't let me, don't let
me, don't let me down I
think I'm losing my mind
now It's in my head,
darling I hope That you'll
be here, when I need you
the most So don't let me,
don't let me, don't let me
down Don't let me down
Yeah, don't let me down
Don't let me down, oh no
Said don't let me down
Don't let me down Don't
let me down Don't let me
down, down, down